# RANJITHPRABHU.K

## **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

- **(** www.ranjithprabhu.in
- ranjithprabhu.k@gmail.com
- +91 9790 650 659

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am passionate in playing with pixels, mostly front end focused. Having good background in web application development. I can do some backend too, but front end sounds more interesting.

4+ years of experience in Full time in the software industry and 4+ years of experience in Part time.

## **EXPERIENCE**

Present SPECIALIST PROGRAMMER

**Infosys Limited - 2.6 Years** 

2016 - 2017 SOFTWARE ENGINEER

**Robert Bosch Engineering & Solutions - 1.2 Years** 

2015 - 2016 SOFTWARE ENGINEER

**KMIT Solutions - 1 Year** 

2010 - 2015 GRAPHIC & WEB DESIGNER

Premier Group of Companies - 4+ Years [Part time]

# **EDUCATION**

2015 M.E. Computer Science & Engg.

**PPG Institute of Technology** 

**CGPA: 8.2** 

2013 M.Sc. Software Systems

Kovai Kalaimagal College of Arts & Science

**CGPA: 8.3** 

**H.S.C.** (+2)

Sri Narayana Matric Higher Secondary School

**62.75** %

**2006** S.S.L.C.

**Government Higher Secondary School** 

84.2 %

#### CERTIFICATION

2010 - 2011 Multimedia Animation Program

**Adora Institute of Multimedia** 

Grade: A+

## **SKILLS**



Angular

React/Redux

**Node JS** 

**Javascript** 

Typescript

\_\_\_\_

Bootstrap

Java

**Springboot** 

Hibernate

Mysal/Monas

Mysql/Mongo — — — — —

Photoshop

Corel Draw

CI / CD

----

# **PROJECTS**

- Oilfield & Well Service Projects
- IOT & Industry 4.0 Projects
- Finance Projects
- E-Commerce Applications
- Dashboard & Admin Applications
- Kiosk Applications
- Reporting Applications
- Data Visualization and Analytics

## **PERSONAL DETAILS**

D.O.B : 05/02/1991

Address: Electronic City Phase II

Bangalore, Karnataka, IN